MARCIN ZRABKOWSKI THIRD ENGINEER



I am an experienced Engineer/Deck Engineer who has been working on various types of vessels over the last many years. I have a vaild US VISA C1/D and B10CS VISA, ITSO, FRC/DC Boatman, UK CEC, 3rd Engineer certificate, BOSIET+CA-EBS, HUET, GWO SEA SURVIVAL, HIGH VOLTAGE I' m looking for new challenges, I learn quickly and I am committed to work.

I am willing to improve my qualifications with new courses.

BORN: 03.08.1992

INTERESTS: ship mechanics, cars, electrics, sport, music, fantasy books

LANGUAGES: English - advanced

EDUCATION MARINE TECHNICAL SCHOOL WITH A

MARINE MECHANIC PROFILE IN

KOLOBRZEG (POLAND)

YEARS OF STUDY 2008-2012

EXPERIENCE

BOKALIFT 2 (Boskalis) HVL DP2 WIND FARM VESSEL as a 3rd Engineer, rotation 6/6weeks from 19.12.2023 - still

PORTLAND SENTINEL (Sentinel Marine) ERRV MULTI ROLE as a 3rd Engineer, rotation 4/4weeks

from 20.03.2022 - 27.10.2023

OCEAN TAY (Atlantic Offshore) ERRV VESSEL as a motorman, rotation 4/4 weeks from 27.08.2021 - 14.01.2022

ULYSSES (Irish Ferries) FERRY VESSEL as a motorman, rotation 6/3 weeks from 13.12.2020 - 01. 07.2021

SCHELDE/WESER HIGHWAY (K-Line) CAR CARRIER VESSEL as a motorman, rotation 12/6 weeks from 31.07.2016 - 24.10.2020

AL RAWDAH (UASC) CONTAINER VESSEL as a motorman from 12.11.2015 - 22.03.2016

CONTACT

MARCIN ZRABKOWSKI marcin.zrabkowski92@gmail.com +48 790340671 78-100 KOLOBRZEG, POLAND

"I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation)".